[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wolverines real name is James Howlett.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which time zone would you find the state of West Virginia?", "correct_answer": "Eastern", "incorrect_answers": ["Central", "Pacific", "Mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The trademarks of Stallone- sarcastic smile, lazy eyes, and slurred speech, are the result of paralysis of the right side of his face.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This pollutant causes inflammation of the lungs, impaired breathing, coughing, chest pain, nausea, and throat irritation and permanent damage to lung tissue in long term exposure.", "correct_answer": "Smog", "incorrect_answers": ["Greenhouse gas", "Carbon dioxide", "Ozone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were born in 1972, with the current year being 2008, the next time your year in the Chinese Zodiac will come around, is 2020.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Box turtles are safe to eat.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to some studies, lycopene, which is found in tomatoes, prevents this disease.", "correct_answer": "Cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Diabetes", "Thrombosis", "Heart attack"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which mass murderer was the inspiration for the movie character Norman Bates in Psycho and  for Buffalo Bill in Silence of the Lambs?", "correct_answer": "Ed Gein", "incorrect_answers": ["Ted Bundy", "Rickie Sperko", "Jeffrey Dahmer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest turtles are aquatic.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actresses did not appear in the 1997 horror movie I Know What You Did Last Summer?", "correct_answer": "Brandy", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah Michelle Gellar", "Jennifer Love Hewitt", "Anne Heche"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which video game console is credited with popularizing the use of game cartridges in 1977?", "correct_answer": "Atari 2600", "incorrect_answers": ["ColecoVision", "NES/Famicom", "Sega Master System"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what war was Fanta developed?", "correct_answer": "WW II", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "The Civil War", "WW I"]}]